<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2024 on Yi Zhu</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/2024/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2024 on Yi Zhu</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/2024/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Cement space No.01</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2024/1-cement-space-no.01/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2024/1-cement-space-no.01/</guid>
      <description>Info Title: Cement space No.01 Year: 2024 Medium: Oil on canvas Size: 100 x 80 cm Description Cement space&#xA;I feel the fragmentation and linearity of the modern city with layers of depth when I was in New York, Hong Kong, Beijing and Shanghai. This feeling is transformed into elements, with a pure special arrangement with structural gaps for growth and survival. Beyond the fragmentation boundary is the struggle for survival and freedom, revealing the purity of the mutual reliance for growth between human and species.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Construct a state of mind</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2024/2-construct-a-state-of-mind-no.01/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2024/2-construct-a-state-of-mind-no.01/</guid>
      <description>Info Left&#xA;Title: Construct a state of mind No.02 Year: 2024 Medium: Oil on canvas Size: 100 x 80 cm Right&#xA;Title: Construct a state of mind No.01 Year: 2024 Medium: Oil on canvas Size: 100 x 80 cm Description Construct a state of mind.&#xA;We cherish the totem of life. We pass on life with heritage. In difficult times, we stay alive to seek beyond.&#xA;Yi Zhu is inspired by the totem and pottery culture of ancient China, along with the papercutting techniques in the Han Dynasty of China.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New species No.01</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2024/5-new-species-no.01/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2024/5-new-species-no.01/</guid>
      <description>Info Title: New species No.01 Year: 2024 Medium: Oil on canvas Size: 80 x 60 cm </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Peach</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2024/6-peach-no.01/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2024/6-peach-no.01/</guid>
      <description>Info Left&#xA;Title: Peach No.01 Year: 2024 Medium: Oil on canvas Size: 50 x 40 cm Right&#xA;Title: Peach No.02 Year: 2024 Medium: Oil on canvas Size: 50 x 40 cm Description Peach&#xA;Growth from youth to maturity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Posthuman implant</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2024/3-posthuman--implant-no.01/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2024/3-posthuman--implant-no.01/</guid>
      <description>Info Left&#xA;Title: Posthuman implant No.01 Year: 2024 Medium: Oil on canvas Size: 100 x 80 cm Right&#xA;Title: Posthuman implant No.02 Year: 2024 Medium: Oil on canvas Size: 100 x 80 cm Description Posthuman implant&#xA;Implantation, when we face AI and the awakening of AI, the implantation of post-human life is the re-creation of life. We want to have a power like AI, but we are overwhelmed by our perception.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Red cloth No.06</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2024/4-red-cloth--no.06/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2024/4-red-cloth--no.06/</guid>
      <description>Info Title: Red cloth No.06 Year: 2024 Medium: Oil on canvas Size: 100 x 80 cm Description Red is a desire.&#xA;What art is might not be an important question.&#xA;Art reveals a dependency between subjectivity and objectivity. It deconstructs and reconstructs the life and world that we are so used to, by utilizing the common structures and space, so that we could sense the spirit of life.&#xA;The series of Red Cloth is a storytelling both inside and outside of the canvas that make us sensed and awake.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
